# **DIVINE OBETEN**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

https://divineobeten2.netlify.app | https://github.com/Deevyn9 divineobeten9@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/divine-obeten

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience. I have experience building responsive and user-friendly websites. I am skilled in developing modern and clean designs and have a passion for creating visually appealing user interfaces. I am always eager to learn and stay up-to-date with the latest technologies and best practices in the industry.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## StunHaul. India (Remote) - Frontend Developer

December 2022 - Present

- Developing responsive and visually appealing user interfaces using ReactJS, CSS and TailwindCSS.
- Maintaining and updating existing web applications to ensure they are performing optimally.
- Participating in code reviews and contributing to the development of new features.

## Intellitech. Remote - Freelance Frontend Developer

November 2022 - December 2022

- Developed and maintained the company's website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Worked closely with the design team to implement responsive and mobile-friendly layout.

## Frontend Mentors. Remote - Volunteer Frontend Developer

August 2021 - Present

- Converting beautiful designs into responsive and dynamic websites and webapps.
- Assisting fellow frontend developers of different experience levels in reviewing websites and codes.
- Helping over 200 frontend developers achieve the best possible solutions to the projects they undertake.

#### PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

Personal Website: <a href="https://divineobeten2.netlify.app">https://divineobeten2.netlify.app</a> (for additional information and projects)

In the World (<a href="https://intheworld.netlify.app">https://intheworld.netlify.app</a>)

- Developed and Tested UI for mobile and desktop.
- Built a brilliant design using React and CSS to satisfy user needs.
- Implemented a Single Page Application using React-router, making use of React-hooks for functionality.

Utilised: React, RestApi, Css, Git, Netlify. Repo Link: https://github.com/Deevyn9/Where-in-the-world

## Comfy Drops (<a href="https://comfydrops.netlify.app">https://comfydrops.netlify.app</a>)

- Designed and Developed a responsive E-Commerce website using React and CSS.
- Alternated between images using a React-bootstrap carousel.
- Managed frontend code using Git version control system.

<u>Utilised:</u> React, CSS, React-bootstrap, Git, Netlify. <u>Repo Link:</u> <a href="https://github.com/Deevyn9/comfy">https://github.com/Deevyn9/comfy</a>

#### **SKILLS**

Proficient: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, JavaScript, React, Figma, Git.

Familiar: TypeScript, Sass.

# **EDUCATION**

Enugu, Nigeria. UNIVERSITY OF NIGERIA

Major: Mechanical Engineering.

Programming Coursework: Fundamentals of C, Operating Systems.

**ME Coursework:** Engineering Thermodynamics, Mechanics of Fluid, Metallurgy, Engineering Design.